<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Pages on Musings of a Developer</title>
    <link>http://niloc.io/page/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Pages on Musings of a Developer</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 27 Dec 2015 22:20:51 -0600</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://niloc.io/page/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>http://niloc.io/about</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Dec 2015 22:20:51 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://niloc.io/about</guid>
      <description>&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Accomplished web engineer with more than 7 years of experience in building for the web.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proven ability to turn an idea into robust, well-tested, maintainable software and get it shipped on spec, on budget, and on time.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Open Source advocate with a strong passion for learning and teaching others.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For the past three years I had been working with Music Dealers, a music licensing startup in Chicago, to build a platform for 20k+ independent musicians to share 200k+ tracks with the world, easily licensable by anybody in the world.  My wife and I are fulfilling a dream of moving west, so I am now looking for a full-time remote or on-site position around Colorado Springs, CO.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My primary goals are to never become stagnant and always continue learning, and to apply the knowledge gained in order to solve real world problems.  I also love teaching the things that I&amp;rsquo;ve learned.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;These days I spend my time working with modern Javascript (Node.js, React.js, Ember.js), Ruby, Python, modern PHP (Laravel), as well as a bit of Golang.  I love writing clean, well documented, and well tested code.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am the founder of CKH Development, a web consulting and development company.  We solve real-world problems by building products that give clients a competitive advantage through a variety of channels.  We focus on building efficient, scalable, and reliable web applications using the tools and technology that best fit the job at hand. If you&amp;rsquo;re looking to build a beautiful product quickly, please &lt;a href=&#34;mailto:me@ckh.io&#34;&gt;get in touch&lt;/a&gt;.  We&amp;rsquo;d love to hear from you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When I&amp;rsquo;m not &amp;ldquo;working,&amp;rdquo; I&amp;rsquo;m usually hacking on personal projects, contributing to the open source software community, or out exploring nature.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Other tid-bits:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;B.S. Computer Science from Purdue University&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I love everything tech &amp;mdash; hardware, software, and everything in-between&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I hate stagnation, and am a big proponent of continuous education&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Open source is the future; embrace it with open arms&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Nature lover &amp;mdash; I spend a lot of time backpacking and camping in the mountains of Colorado&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>